lkrsocialmedia.com 2019-11-28

# MeetEdgar Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Roeder Studios, Inc., the owner and operator of the Edgar application, and we are committed to protecting your personal information. In this policy, we are letting you know about the ways we collect and use your information, so you can make an informed choice regarding whether you will use Edgar.

By using Edgar, you consent to the terms of this policy.

This privacy policy was last changed on May 25th, 2018, to address Personal Information collection, retention, and access.

 **What information do we collect?**

When you sign up to use Edgar, we collect your name, email address, IP address, credit card information, and other information necessary to process your transaction.

When you link your Edgar account with supported Social Media Platforms such as Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn, we may have access to information regarding your Social Media Platform accounts, and you will be notified at that time regarding what information we can access.

We collect non-identifiable personal information through the use of “cookies.” A cookie is a small data file that a Web site can transfer to your hard drive through your browser. The cookie is then stored on your computer as an anonymous tag. You can set your browser to notify you if cookies are received. If you choose to set up your browser to not accept cookies, you will not be able to use Edgar.

We may collect some other personally identifying information about your transaction in a non-identifiable format and combine it with other non-identifiable information, to be analyzed only at an aggregate level. We will use anonymized data from your account to improve the service for all customers. We will not use the content you post except to internally improve our systems.

We have a public blog on our Websites. Any information you include in a comment on our blog may be read, collected, and used by anyone. If your Personal Information appears on our blogs and you want it removed, contact us at [support@meetedgar.com](mailto:support@meetedgar.com). If we are unable to remove your information, we will tell you why.

Our Websites include links to other websites, whose privacy practices may be different from ours. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Website you visit.

 **What information do we share with Third Parties?**

We may disclose Personal Information to third party service providers who help us provide and support our Services. For example, if it is necessary to provide you something you have requested (like enabling posting to social media platforms), then we may share your Personal Information with a Service Provider for that purpose. Examples of Service Providers include payment processors, hosting services and content delivery services.

 **How Do We Use Your Information?**

We use your name and email to send you periodic emails, including email newsletters and occasional business announcements and updates.

We use your credit card to process your transaction. We may use your email to contact you about your account.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so we can optimize our website and create a better user experience for you.

 **Where do we operate?**

Our servers and offices are located in the United States, so your information may be transferred to, stored, or processed in the United States. While the data protection, privacy, and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, we take many steps to protect your privacy. By using our Websites, you understand and consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this policy.

 **How do we update and retain data?**

We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do so. If your data changes (for example, if you have a new email address), then you are responsible for notifying us of those changes. Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your Personal Information. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as needed to provide you with our Services. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our Agreements.

 **How can I access my stored personal information?**

Individuals may request to access, correct, amend or delete information we hold about them by emailing [support@meetedgar.com](mailto:support@meetedgar.com).  Personal Information includes name, address, email, IP address, social media platform names, and social media account access tokens. Unless it is prohibited by law, we will remove any Personal Information about an individual, either you or a Subscriber, from our servers at your or their request. For users in the EU, we will comply with timelines dictated by the governing authority (currently within 30 days of the request). There is no charge for an individual to access or update their Personal Information.

 **Do We Respond to Do Not Track Signals?**

Do Not Track is a privacy setting you can change in your website browser, so your activities cannot be tracked from website to website. We do not respond to Do Not Track signals in browsers, because we do not track your activities across different websites.

 **How Do You Unsubscribe?**

You must maintain a working email address associated with your Edgar account, so you can receive email regarding your Edgar account. However, if at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving promotional emails, you can opt-out by unsubscribing at the bottom of any email we send to you.

 **How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We use various security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information, including hosting your data on a secure server and/or a third-party password-protected, secure service. Any third-party secure service we use will keep your information confidential, will not sell or share your information, and will not contact you directly. Billing and payment data are encrypted whenever transmitted or received online.

We share your information with specific third parties who assist us in taking care of you (such as the password-protected, secure service above), who agree to keep your information confidential. We will also release your information as required by law or if necessary to protect our legal rights, to comply with a judicial proceeding or court order, to prevent abuse of Edgar, or to prevent threats to others or illegal activities.

We have no control over how the various Social Media Platforms collect or use your identifying information that you supply to them directly. Please refer to the privacy policies of those companies for more information about how they use your information.

Edgar doesn’t store your Social Media Platform passwords. We receive and store access tokens from your Social Media Platform accounts in order to have continued access for posting and to provide statistics back to you related to those posts. Access to your accounts are only done through the APIs. You can log in to your social media accounts to view, modify, and/or revoke this access. If you choose to modify or revoke, Edgar will not be able to post on your behalf.

Edgar uses [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) for all customer billing (see <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>)

Edgar uses [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/) for email list management (see <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>)

Edgar operates its app on the [Heroku](https://www.heroku.com/) platform (see <https://www.heroku.com/policy/privacy>)

Edgar encrypts data through SSL certificates provided by [Let’s Encrypt](https://letsencrypt.org/) (see <https://letsencrypt.org/privacy/>), [Alpha SSL](https://www.alphassl.com/) (see <https://www.globalsign.com/en/repository/GlobalSign_CP_v5.2.pdf>), and [Cloudflare](https://www.cloudflare.com/) (see <https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/>)

We store name and email address collected through form submissions on our site through our web host, [WPEngine ](https://wpengine.com/)(see <https://wpengine.com/legal/privacy/>)

Our blog uses [Disqus ](https://disqus.com/)to allow for comments on articles and posts (see <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>)

Our team uses [Intercom](https://www.intercom.io/) to provide support for our app. We store your full name, address, email, social media profile name, and job title in the service.

We use [Mixpanel](https://mixpanel.com/) for analytics and tracking. We store name, email, and IP Address in the service.

Circumstances may arise where we may decide to sell, buy, merge, or otherwise reorganize our business in the United States or elsewhere, or where we may decide to share, rent, buy, or sell business assets for the purpose of reorganizing, developing, or expanding our business. It is our policy to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. In the event that our entire company or the Edgar application asset is acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

 **Information Regarding Children**

We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. This website, products, and services are not directed to people who are under 13 years of age. Please notify us at support@meetedgar.com. if you are a parent whose child has provided us with personally identifying information, and we will delete such information from our files.

 **Questions Regarding This Policy**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please direct them to: [support@meetedgar.com](mailto:support@meetedgar.com).
